RG 062:070 Town of Killingworth
Connecticut State Library
Town of Killingworth records
1777-1932
Connecticut State Library
Killingworth (Conn.)
7.25 cubic feet
Administrative, tax, and school records for the town of Killingworth.
RG062_070
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Killingworth was named in May 1667.
Scope and Content
Administrative, tax, and school records for the town of Killingworth.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Schools -- Connecticut -- Killingworth -- History -- Sources; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Killingworth -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Killingworth -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Killingworth -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Killingworth -- Registers
Places:
Killingworth (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1777-1932
  - T000388
    - Rate books, 1777-1788, undated (Box Box 1)
    - Second Society rate book, 1815-1817 (Box Box 1)
    - Register of dog taxes
      - 1915-1921, 1 volume (Box Box 2)
    - Tax abstracts, 1831-1932
      Tax abstracts for 1919 to 1932 are not boxed.
      - 1831, 1832, 1833, 1834, 1835, 1835, 1836, 1837, 1838, 1839 (Box Box 3)
        There are separate tax abstracts for the 1st and 2nd societies for years 1834 and 1835.
      - 1841, 1842, 1843, 1844, 1845, 1846, 1847, 1848, 1849 (Box Box 4)
      - 1850-1851, 1852, 1853-1854, 1855-1856, 1857-1859, 1860-1862, 1863-1864, 1865-1866, 1867-1868, 1869-1870 (Box Box 5)
      - 1871-1873, 1874-1876, 1875-1879, 1877-1879, 1880-1882, 1883-1884, 1885-1887, 1888-1892 (Box Box 6)
      - 1893-1896, 1897-1904, 1905-1907, 1908-1909, 1910, 1911-1913 (Box Box 7)
      - 1914-1916, 1917-1918 (Box Box 8)
        On oversize shelving.
      - 1919-1920, 1 volume
      - 1921-1922, 1 volume
      - 1923-1924, 1 volume
      - 1925-1926, 1 volume
      - 1927, 1 volume
      - 1928-1929, 1 volume
      - 1930-1931, 1 volume
      - 1932, 1 volume
  - 1984-031
    - First School Society records, 1797-1837; 1 volume (Box Box 9)